const contest_2_1 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Each school will be presented with the configuration of the valence shell electrons of an element. State if the element is likely to be a metal or a non-metal or a metalloid. Give your reason based on the electron configuration only.",
        "Question": "$4 s^{2} 4 p^{2}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A metalloid: It will not form a cation easily neither will it form an anion easily. It will tend to have the properties of both metals and non-metals.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Each school will be presented with the configuration of the valence shell electrons of an element. State if the element is likely to be a metal or a non-metal or a metalloid. Give your reason based on the electron configuration only.",
        "Question": "$3 s^{2}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A metal: It will form a cation easily hence will behave as a metal.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Each school will be presented with the configuration of the valence shell electrons of an element. State if the element is likely to be a metal or a non-metal or a metalloid. Give your reason based on the electron configuration only.",
        "Question": "$5 s^{2} 5 p^{5}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A non-metal: It will form an anion easily, hence it will behave as a non-metal.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$15.0 \\mathrm{~g}$ of a sample of soil was dried in the oven until a constant weight of $14.3 \\mathrm{~g}$ was obtained. Find the percentage moisture in the original soil.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Moisture in the soil $=15.0-14.3=0.700 \\mathrm{~g}$\n$$\n\\text { \\%Moisture }=\\frac{0.700}{15.0} \\times 100=4.67\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A piece of wood weighing $205 \\mathrm{~g}$ was immersed in water for $12.0 \\mathrm{hrs}$, taken out, wiped dry and weighed. This was repeated until a constant weight of $207.2 \\mathrm{~g}$ was obtained. Calculate the percentage water content of the wood after it was immersed in water.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Amount of water absorbed $=207.2-205=2.20$\n$$\n\\text { \\%Water }=\\frac{2.20}{207.2} \\times 100=1.06\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$4.00 \\mathrm{~g}$ of a metal was burnt in excess air to give $5.60 \\mathrm{~g}$ of its oxide. Determine the percentage oxygen in the oxide.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Mass of oxygen that reacted $=5.60-4.00=1.60$ $\\%$ Oxygen in the oxide $=\\frac{1.60}{5.60} \\times 100=28.6$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which phylum is characterized by the presence of a notochord?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Chordata",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Name the first group of vertebrates which possessed amniotic egg?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Amphibia",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which phylum of organisms has a water vascular system?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Echinodermata",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe population of organism with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Type of competition that occurs among individuals",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Intra-specific competition occurs among the individuals of a population",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe population of organism with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Morphology and behaviour of individuals",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "The individuals in a population are morphologically and behaviorally similar",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe population of organism with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Number of species that make up a population",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A population consists of a single species",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "From a point $P$ outside a circle, a tangent is drawn to touch the circle at $T$. From $P$ a line is drawn to cut the circle at $A$ and $B$.",
        "Question": "Find the length of $P T$ given $P A=9 \\mathrm{~cm}$ and $A B=11 \\mathrm{~cm}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "PT $=6 \\sqrt{5} \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$$\n\\left[\\mathrm{PA}=9, \\mathrm{~PB}=9+11=20, \\mathrm{PT}^{2}=\\mathrm{PA} \\times \\mathrm{PB}=9 \\times 20=180, \\mathrm{PT}=\\sqrt{180}=6\\sqrt{5}\\right]\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "From a point $P$ outside a circle, a tangent is drawn to touch the circle at $T$. From $P$ a line is drawn to cut the circle at $A$ and $B$.",
        "Question": "Find the length of $P A$ given $P T=30 \\mathrm{~cm}$ and $P B=20 \\mathrm{~cm}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "PA $=45 \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$$\n\\left[\\mathrm{PT}^{2}=\\mathrm{PA} \\times \\mathrm{PB}, \\mathrm{PA}=\\mathrm{PT}^{2} / \\mathrm{PB}=30^{2} / 20=900 / 20=45\\right]\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "From a point $P$ outside a circle, a tangent is drawn to touch the circle at $T$. From $P$ a line is drawn to cut the circle at $A$ and $B$.",
        "Question": "Find the length of $P B$ given $P A=18 \\mathrm{~cm}$, and $P T=24 \\mathrm{~cm}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "PB = $32 \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$\\left[\\mathrm{PT}^{2}=\\mathrm{PA} \\times \\mathrm{PB}, \\mathrm{PB}=\\mathrm{PT}^{2} / \\mathrm{PA}=24 \\times 24 / 18=8 \\times 8 / 2=32\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Determine the constants $A$ and $B$ if",
        "Question": "$(2 x-3) /(x-2)=A+B /(x-2) \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$A=2, B=1$\n$[2 x-3=A(x-2)+B$, compare coefficients $A=2,-3=-4+B, B=1]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Determine the constants $A$ and $B$ if",
        "Question": "$(3 x+5) /(x+3)=A+B /(x+3) \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$A=3, B=-4$\n$\\left[3 x+5=A(x+3)+B\\right.$, for $x$ coefficients $3=A$, for $x^{0} \\quad 5=3 A+B$,\n$B=5-9=-4]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Determine the constants $A$ and $B$ if",
        "Question": "$(5 x+6) /(x-1)=A+B /(x-1) \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$A=5, B=11$\n$\\left[5 x+6=A(x-1)+B\\right.$, for $x$ coefficients $A=5$, for $\\left.x^{0} 6=B-A, B=5+6=11\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the kinetic energy of a uniform $2.0 \\mathrm{~m}$ long solid rod of diameter $0.20 \\mathrm{~m}$ when it rotates about the given axis at $0.50 \\mathrm{rad} \\mathrm{s}^{-1}$. The mass of the rod is $32 \\mathrm{~kg}$.",
        "Question": "An axis perpendicular to the axis of the rod and passing through its center.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$1.3 \\mathrm{~J}$\n$$\nK=M L^{2} \\omega^{2} / 24=32 \\mathrm{~kg} \\times(2.0 \\mathrm{~m})^{2} \\times\\left(0.50 \\mathrm{rad} \\mathrm{s}^{-1}\\right)^{2} / 24=1.3 \\mathrm{~J}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the kinetic energy of a uniform $2.0 \\mathrm{~m}$ long solid rod of diameter $0.20 \\mathrm{~m}$ when it rotates about the given axis at $0.50 \\mathrm{rad} \\mathrm{s}^{-1}$. The mass of the rod is $32 \\mathrm{~kg}$.",
        "Question": "An axis perpendicular to and crossing the axis of the rod $0.50 \\mathrm{~m}$ from one end.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$2.3 \\mathrm{~J}$\n$$\nK=M \\omega^{2}\\left(L^{2} / 12+d^{2}\\right) / 2=32 \\mathrm{~kg} \\times\\left(0.50 \\mathrm{rad} \\mathrm{s}^{-1}\\right)^{2} \\times\\left[\\left(2.0 \\mathrm{~m}^{2} / 12+(0.5 \\mathrm{~m})^{2}\\right] / 2=2.3 \\mathrm{~J}\\right.\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the kinetic energy of a uniform $2.0 \\mathrm{~m}$ long solid rod of diameter $0.20 \\mathrm{~m}$ when it rotates about the given axis at $0.50 \\mathrm{rad} \\mathrm{s}^{-1}$. The mass of the rod is $32 \\mathrm{~kg}$.",
        "Question": "An axis that coincides with the axis of the rod.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$0.080 \\mathrm{~J}$\n$$\nK=M R^{2} \\omega^{2} / 4=32 \\mathrm{~kg} \\times(0.20 \\mathrm{~m})^{2} \\times\\left(0.50 \\mathrm{rads}^{-1}\\right)^{2} / 4=0.080 \\mathrm{~J}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The quantity of an ideal gas is $0.20 \\mathrm{~mol}$ and the slope of an isobar on a $V-T$ diagram for the gas is $8.3 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}$. Find the pressure of the gas.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$0.20 \\mathrm{~Pa}$\n$$\nP=n R / m=0.20 \\mathrm{~mol} \\times 8.31 \\mathrm{Jmol}^{-1} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1} /\\left(8.3 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}\\right)=0.20 \\mathrm{~Pa}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The slope of an ideal gas isobar on a $V-T$ diagram is $0.041 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}$. Find the pressure of the gas if the quantity of the gas is $7.4 \\mathrm{~mol}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$1500 \\mathrm{~Pa}$\n$$\nP=n R / m=7.4 \\mathrm{~mol} \\times 8.31 \\mathrm{Jmol}^{-1} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1} /\\left(0.041 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}\\right)=1500 \\mathrm{~Pa}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The slope of an ideal gas isobar on a $V-T$ diagram is $0.060 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}$. Find the number of moles of the gas if its pressure is $250 \\mathrm{~Pa}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$1.8 \\mathrm{~mol}$\n$$\nn=P m / R=250 \\mathrm{~Pa} \\times 0.060 \\mathrm{~m}^{3} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1} /\\left(8.31 \\mathrm{Jmol}^{-1} \\mathrm{~K}^{-1}\\right)=1.8 \\mathrm{~mol}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    }
]

export default contest_2_1